nice to meet you.
初めまして
That's why I'm suddenly saying this,
いきなりこんなこと言うのもあれなんですけど、
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いですね
not at all.
全然
I'm a little surprised.
ちょっとびっくりしてます
Too cute.
可愛すぎて
Huh, if it's this cute,
え、なんか、こんだけ可愛かったら、
Do you do anything in the entertainment industry?
芸能系とかやってたりするんですか?
Ah, well, a little.
ああ、まぁ、若干
Can I call it entertainment-related?
芸能系って言っていいのかな?
What do you usually do now?
今は普段は何をされてるんですか?
It's like an Instagrammer.
は、一応インスタグラマーみたいな
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうですね
Entertainment.
芸能系
I don't go into an office or anything.
事務所とかには入ってないですね
It's not included though.
とかには入ってないんですけど
I see.
なるほど
Looks like an Instagrammer.
インスタグラマーっぽいですね
Isn't it like that?
ぽいですかね
I don't know.
わかんない
Just my image.
俺のイメージだけ
Instagrammers are quite like that.
インスタグラマーってさ、結構その、
After all, what do you call it, looks paper?
やっぱり、 何て言うんだろう、ルックス用紙?
After all, you can't do it properly, can you?
や っぱり、良くちゃんとできないんですか?
But I don't really show my face.
でも、顔とか別に出してないんで
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうなんですね
Are you not showing your face?
顔は出してないですか?
I don't show my face.
顔は出してないです
Why did I put it out, even though it seemed like it would work?
なんで出したら、なんか、いけそうなのに
Why should I take it out?
なんで出したらいいの?
Somehow,
なんか、
I don't know what it is, but it's a little known to those around me.
何 だろう、周りに知られるのがちょっと
Oh, wait.
あ、ちょっと
I'm still a little embarrassed.
まだ、 ちょっと恥ずかしい
I see.
そっか
なるほどね
Well then, from behind, like the back of your head,
じゃあ、よく、 後ろから、自分の後頭部みたいな、
Like from behind.
後ろからみたいな
Oh, let me take some pictures.
ああ、ちょっと撮ってもらったり
Like below the neck.
首下みたいな
And what about the number of followers now?
それに今、フォロワー数的には?
There are about 10,000 people now.
今は、1万人くらいですかね
That's amazing.
すごいっすね
10,000 people should already be monetized, right?
1万人ってもう収益化するんじゃないですか?
I agree.
そうですね
You know.
知ってますね
Oh no.
やば
Instagram.
インスタグラム
I've heard that it's kind of popular.
なんか、流行ってるとは聞くんですよ
I hear it's popular.
流行ってるとは聞くんですけど
Is it up to Instagram?
インスタグラムまでですか
But I think it's easy to get started, and there are a lot of them.
でも、始めやすいし、多いんじゃないですかね
I guess so.
そうなのかな
Well, here too.
まあ、ここにもね
The camera is rolling right now.
今のともカメラ回っちゃってるんですけど
Usually, a lot of photos are taken,
普段じゃあ、写真いっぱい撮られてるから、
Are you not too nervous?
あんまり緊張してないですか?
Are you nervous?
緊張してますか?
Yeah, yeah, a little bit.
うん、うん、ちょっと
It feels a little different.
ちょっと感じ違いますね
By the way, what kind of management is it?
ちなみに、どういう経営なんですか?
Is that the one you're riding?
乗せてるやつですか?
Cafes, photos, etc.
カフェとか、写真とか
Photos from when I often went there.
よ く行った時の写真とか
Hmm.
うーん
So, something like that.
じゃあ、そういう、なんか
That's okay, I don't really understand it, so
いいっすね、ちょっと僕はあんま分かってないんで、
I can't dig deep though.
深掘れないですけど
You're an Instagrammer.
インスタグラマーさんですね
If you show your face, more.
顔出ししたらね、もっと
Because it's so cute.
こんなに可愛いから
Follow more.
もっとフォロワーする
It seems to be a buzz though.
バズいそうなんですけど
Well, what do you think?
いやー、どうですかね
There are no plans for now.
今のところは、予定はない
Eh, but,
え、でもさ、
Instagrammers don't show their faces.
イ ンスタグラマーの方で顔出し出してないですよね
I'm really interested in this now.
今、これ、気に映っちゃってます
face.
顔
Followers, are you interested?
フォロワー、気の?
Ah, but this and that.
あ、でもこれ、あれですね
It's not something you should post on the internet.
ネットに載せるとかじゃないやつですもんね
Oh, well, yeah.
あ、まあまあ、そうそう
Ah, then is it okay?
あ、なら、大丈夫かな?
Well, yeah, yeah.
まあまあ、そうそう
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味は何かあるんですか?
As for my hobbies, I like going around cafes.
趣味は、カフェ巡りとかやっぱり好きですかね
It's called a cafe.
カフェってね
I agree.
そうですね
Do you go to cafes all over Japan?
日本全国のカフェ行ったりするんですか?
All over Japan, even though it's such a far away place,
日本全国、そんな遠いところはあれだけど、
I'll probably go look for something nearby.
近場で、 うん、探して行ったりとか
Well, let's do something we like on YouTube that was popular for a while.
じゃ、なんか、前で一時流行ったYouTubeの好きなことして
I'm just going to live my life, isn't it? I guess that's what it feels like.
生 きていくじゃないですか、そういう感じに近いんですかね、
It's an extension of my hobby.
趣味の延長というか
Well, it might be like that.
そうですね、そんな感じかも
What do you do on your day off?
お休みの日は何してるんですか?
On my day off, I'm going to wear it now, but...
お休みの日は、まあちょっと今かぶっちゃうけど、
I go there with friends.
それこそ友達とか行ったり
Or something like that.
行ったりとかですかね
Where have you been lately?
最近どこ行った?
Was it good to go where you went?
行ったところで行っちゃうところがよかったですか?
Is it Korea?
韓国ですかね
Ah, Korea, right?
あ、 韓国ですかね
What are you doing in Korea?
韓国で何してるんですか?
I buy clothes and cosmetics, and go to cafes in town.
洋服とかコスメ買ったり、街のカフェとかも行ったり
It's nice, it's glittering.
いいっすね、きらびやかです
dazzling.
眩しい
Isn't it dazzling?
眩しいですかね
You have really good style.
めちゃめちゃスタイルが良いですよね
It's like Instagram.
イ ン スタグラムっぽい
Isn't it like that?
ぽいですかね
Is this a skirt?
これスカートなんですか?
This is a skirt, I'm wearing a dress.
これスカートです、ワンピースやって
Like the feel of the fabric?
生地感とか?
material?
生地?
normal mid.
普通のミッド
Ah, no, just the feel of the fabric.
あ、いいや普通に生地感をね
Isn't it a bit too sexy?
ちょっとセクシーすぎないですか、
This clothes.
この服
sexy.
セクシー
Just a little bit, around here.
ちょっとね、この辺とかね
I can see it.
見えちゃってる
What is this?
これ何?
Show off?
見せぶら?
No, normal.
いや、普通の
Eh, normal?
え、普通のの?
A normal one.
普通のやつ
What, can you see it?
え、見えちゃってるの?
Well, that's about it.
まあ、ここくらいだったの
TRUE?
本当?
Such a beautiful person.
こんな綺麗な人が
Why did you come to this place?
なんでこういうところに来てくれたんですか?
Ah, but I've been interested in it for a while now.
あー、でもちょっと前から興味があって
I'm interested.
興味があって
picture?
え?
I guess I should say that.
といってみようかなみたいな
I'm interested in being taken for something a little naughty.
ちょっとえっちゃなことに、とられることに興味がある
I agree.
そうですね
I see.
そっか
In terms of whether I like or dislike naughty things.
え っちゃなことは好きか嫌いかで言うと
If I have to say whether I like it or not, I still like it.
好 きか嫌いで言ったら、まだ好きです
Well, stop it.
じゃあ、やめに
Can I ask you something?
ちょっと聞いていい?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
What kind of play do you like?
どういうプレイが好きとかある?
What kind of play?
どういうプレイ?
What, for example?
どういう、例えば?
I wonder what it is.
何だろう
Well, is it normal or outdoors?
まあ、ノーマルなのか、 野外なのか、
Is it a sci-fi chick?
SFチックなのかとか
No, but it's just normal.
いやー、でも普通にノーマルかな
Have you ever done anything unusual?
今まで変わったやつとかしたことある?
Some strange places.
変わった場所とか
No, not at all.
いや、全然ないです
Just normal play.
本当に普通のプレイしか
Have you ever caught it?
とらえたことはありますか?
No, not really.
いや、ないですね
do not have?
ない?
first time?
初めて?
It's my first time.
初めてです
So, today is my first unusual experience.
じゃあ、今日が初めての変わったやつですね
I'll ask you some questions today.
今日問いながらするからね
Have you ever tried something like that?
おなにとかしたことある?
I've done everything before.
おなにもしたことはあります
Do you usually do it?
普段する?
Once in a while.
たまーに
How many weeks?
週、どれくらいで
I wonder how much.
どんくらいだろう
About once or twice?
1、2回くらい?
Is that, erm, a finger?
それは、えっと、指?
With toys.
おもちゃで
Ah, but it's a finger.
あ、でも指かな
What about fingers?
指なんて
Yeah.
うん
Where is your erogenous body?
どこが性感体ですか?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
But I feel the chestnuts the most.
でも、くりが一番感じる
What is chestnut?
くりって何?
where?
どこ?
Where is chestnut?
くりってどこ?
The one above?
上の方?
I don't really understand, so could you please prick me with your finger?
ちょっと分かんないんで、僕、指刺してもらっていいですか?
refer to?
指?
My own?
自分の?
Ah, okay.
あ、いいです
That's fine there.
そこでいいです
Is it above this?
この上かな?
Then?
そしたら?
That place is called chestnut.
そこ、くりって言うんだ
Where is the chestnut?
くりがあるのはどこですか?
What do you call female genitalia?
女性器は何て言いますか?
what?
なん?
What do you say?
なんて言う?
What is it?
なんだよ、かな?
what
なん
in?
で?
kana?
かな?
cute.
か わいい
To such a beautiful person, such a cute person.
こんなきれいな人に、かわいい人に
In this way, I, for a moment, need something more.
こうして、僕、ちょっと、もう何か、
It's gotten a little bigger.
ちょっと大きくなっちゃった
Get a little stiff.
ちょっと、固くなって
Did you touch me?
触ってくれたんですか?
Did you touch me a little?
ちょっと触ってくれたんですか?
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
What do you think of this?
どうですか、これ
There really is a little bit.
本当にちょっとあるんですね
It sounds interesting.
興味ある感じなんですね
What do you think of this?
どうですか、これ
It's hard.
固いです
固 いです
I just want to feel better.
ちょっと、気持ちよくしたいですけど
By the way, the place you just touched is
ち なみに、今、触ってくれたところは、
What do you say?
何て言うところですか?
What are you reading?
なんて読んでるかな?
Chin Chin?
ちんちん?
Look at the camera and see my dick.
カメラ見て、ちんちんまんこって
Can I have you do it while I do the pieces?
ピースしながらやってもらっていいですか?
While doing peace?
ピースしながら?
one hand?
片手?
Please use both hands.
両手でお願いします
It's my hedge.
僕のヘッジなんですよ
sorry.
すみません
I'm going to do some hedging, but are you mentally prepared?
ヘッジなことしちゃいますけど、 心の準備はOKですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Usually, for example, travel scenery, food, etc.
普段、例えば旅行風景とか、ご飯とか、
I often see myself reflected from behind.
い っぱい、自分も後ろから映ってるよね
I think I've been photographed, but today...
撮られてると思うけど、 今日は、
Comint, it's a hedge,
コミントとか、 ヘッジなところさ、
I'll take lots of pictures though.
いっぱい撮っちゃうけど
Oh no, it really is.
やばい、もう本当に
It's too bad.
もう やばい
It's true.
本当だ
I think that's going to happen.
そうなっちゃいけそう
Do you hate me?
俺が嫌なのかな?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Your face is so small.
顔ちっちゃいね
Is that so?
そうですかね
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと 待ってみてね
I don't think so myself.
自分では思わないけど
Isn't it half?
半 分じゃないの?
Because I'm wearing a mask.
マスクしてるから
I don't really understand it though.
あんまよく分かんないけど
Even when I wear a mask, my face doesn't look any smaller.
マスクしたら、でも結構ちっちゃくならない顔って
Because I don't know the outline.
輪郭とか分かんないから
surely.
確かに
I'm nervous.
緊張してますね
Well then, let me give you a spell to relieve your tension.
じゃあ、緊張が取れるおまじないしてあげようか
what kind?
どんな?
Is there a spell?
おまじない?
You might have heard a little bit about it.
ちょっと聞いたかもしれない
Did you hear?
聞いた?
I might have heard about it.
ちょっと聞いたかも
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃない?
Being touched.
触られて
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Don't understand something?
何か分からない?
About C?
Cくらい?
C from G.
GよりのC
It might not be that big.
あんまり大きい方ではないかも
I don't think it's important at all.
大事なのが、全然あると思うけどね
What's important is the shape.
大事なのが、形だからさ
Size doesn't matter.
大きさなんて、別に
While being stuffed.
のっぱいされながらさ
That may not be the case though.
そう いうことでもないかもしれないけど
good?
いい?
It's soft.
柔らかいね
I'm so excited.
めっちゃ興奮するな
good?
いい?
Even if I get a little excited.
ちょっと興奮しても
Below, it's tangled.
下、絡まっちゃったよ
Did you get tangled?
絡まっちゃった?
See you tomorrow.
明日ね
Okay, wait a minute, camera now.
じゃあさ、ちょっとさ、カメラの方今、
With this face, just show it off a little.
この顔でさ、ちょっとぴったり出して
cute.
可愛い
You're a little too cute, can I hug you?
ちょっと可愛すぎるからさ、抱きしめていい?
Here now.
こっち今
Do you want a girlfriend like this?
こんな彼女欲しいの?
That's right.
当たってる
Chichin?
ちいちん?
Chi-chin?
ち いちん?
I can't help it, just a little,
ちょっと我慢できないけどさ、ちょっとだけさ、
It's close.
近いな
Have you ever taken a deep breath?
深呼吸したことある?
Yeah.
うん
I have a lot to do today, but I've already done it.
今日は いっぱいさ、もうしてるけどさ、
You're doing something naughty, aren't you?
イッチなことしてるんだよね
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいないの?
but.
でも
Yeah, not really.
うん、ないですね
A sex friend?
セフレとか?
To this Moots?
このムーツに?
He came.
来てくれた
Your feet are white.
足、白いね
Your legs are thin.
細いね、足ね
I could see my pants.
パンツ見えちゃった
I could see your pants.
ポ ンツ パンツ見えちゃった
Can I have you entrust me with the pants myself?
自分でポンツ託し上げてもらっていい?
Can I entrust you with my skirt?
スカート託し上げてもらっていい?
Ponts.
ポンツね
Itch.
イッチ
Why here?
ここなんで?
Can I take a closer look here?
ここさ、もっと近くで見ていい?
Nearby?
近くで?
in?
で?
here?
ここ?
I can't take it anymore.
もう我慢できない
Take off your clothes.
服脱いでよ
Look at my underwear.
下着見して
I really like the style.
めっちゃスタイルいいね
Do you usually pay attention to anything?
普段何か気をつけてるの?
I'm not really careful.
あんまり気をつけてはない
So this is it.
それで これなんだ
Can I take a closer picture?
もっと近くで撮っていい?
Try raising your arms.
両腕上げてみて
Use both elbows too.
両肘も使ってね
It might be a little embarrassing.
ちょっと脇恥ずかしいかも
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a beautiful color.
綺麗な色だね
I'll put the camera down for a moment.
ちょっと一回カメラ置くわ
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
I went.
行っちゃった
Let's go
行 っちゃ
That's right.
った んだね
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
めっちゃ綺麗でしょ
Elementary school, upper grades, etc.
小学校、高学年とか
What should I do?
どうしよう?
I've been wearing it since then.
そのくらいからつけて
I wonder what it's like.
ど ーんじゃないかな
I don't remember much though.
あんまり覚えてないけど
tickles?
くすぐったい?
A little aside.
ちょっと脇は
It might be exhausting.
く す ぐったいかも
tickles.
くすぐったい
All you need to do is get ticklish.
くすぐったいは近づけただけでいい
Just bring it closer.
近づけただけでいい
tickles.
くすぐったい
Does your neck tickle?
首くすぐったいか
too.
も
tickles.
く すぐったい
Try stretching your hips.
腰伸ばしてみて
I really like the style.
めっちゃスタイルいいね
Which one would you like to have a tighter fit?
しっくりとくりだったら、 どっちつまってほしい?
Kurikana.
くりかな
Do you prefer chestnuts?
くりのほうが好き?
Then sit down.
じゃあ座って
I've been able to clean it.
掃除できてるよ
Hey, are your pants a little stained?
てかさ、 ちょっとさ、パンツ しみてる?
Does it stain?
しみてる?
Yeah.
うん
This attitude is a bit annoying.
この姿勢がちょっと いっちゃったから
Because I'm gone.
い っちゃったから
Is it starting to seep in?
しみてきてる?
yes.
そう
The pants are a little strange.
パンツはちょっと おかしい
It's true.
本当だ
da
ダ
Blue peace.
ブ ルピースして
So close.
こんな近くで
It's weak.
くり弱いね
now
今
Come on!
い っちゃってさ
Well then, wait a minute, let's put on your underwear.
じゃあさ、 ちょっとさ、さっき 下着もさ、
I saw it while standing.
立ちながら見たじゃん
I was looking at the skin on my nose too.
鼻皮もさ、 見てたなって
Go, wet pussy,
行ってさ、 のれぬれのまんこさ、
I want you to open it yourself and show it to me.
自分で開いて見せてほしい
oh yeah.
そうそう
Do you want to expand as much as possible?
思いっきり広げる?
Spread as much as you can
思いっきり広げ
Ru?
る?
Have you never done it?
や ったことない?
I've never done it.
やったことない
picture,
え、
do not have.
ない
Would you like to see it?
見て みる?
No, it's a little embarrassing.
いや、ちょっと恥ずかしい
Like this.
こんな感じで
Because it's wet, right in front of my dick.
ぬれてるからさ、 ちんちんの前にさ、
You'll really get sucked into it.
めっちゃ吸い付いてもらうよね
Okay, fingers.
いいよ、指
Hands are fine.
手、いいよ
Try straining it on your elbows.
肘ついて上段こしてみて
It's a little hard.
ちょっと硬いって
Leave it out.
抜かして
copper?
どう?
Well then, put on your clothes.
じゃあさ、間着て
Bring your face closer to Jin-kun.
顔をさ、じんくんに近づけて
I don't say anything at all.
全然なんか、 言うしない
Well then,
じゃあさ、
Well then, while you're at it, just say it out loud.
じゃあ、 さもりながら、 とばのべて
Okay, Toba.
いいよ、とば
I want a penis.
ちんちんほしい
Should I do it raw?
生でしよっか
Don't wear rubber?
ゴムつけない?
I wanted to do it live.
生でしたいなと思って
Have you ever done it live?
生でしたことある?
in the first place.
そもそも
Have you ever done it live?
生でしたことない?
Not really.
ないね
Let's try it.
してみようよ
It's different from rubber.
ゴムと違うよ
It feels good, raw.
気持ちいいよ、生の
Are you interested?
興味ある?
I want to try it raw.
生でしてみたい
I asked her to put a raw penis in me.
生のもちんちん入れてくださいって言って
Do you say it?
言うの?
While looking at the camera.
カメラ見ながら
Please put some raw penis in it.
生のもちんちん入れてくださいって
It feels so good.
め っちゃ気持ちいい
Spread your legs, make a double piece with both hands,
足広げて、 両手でダブルピースして、
Okay, raise your back a little bit, just raise your upper body.
じゃあ、 後ろちょっと上げて、 上半身だけ上げて
It feels so good, I feel like I'm going to come out.
ちょっとさ、 気持ちよすぎて、 出ちゃいそう
Can I take it out for a while?
ちょっと出していい?
Can I take it out for a moment?
ちょっと 出していい?
I'll really give it out.
ほんと出すよ
It just came out.
ちょっと出てきた
Stretch out your arms.
腕伸ばして
腕 伸ばして
This kind of thing comes out a lot.
めっちゃ出てる、こういうの
look?
見 る?
Wow, that's true.
すごい、ほんとだ
Was it okay to let it inside?
中に出してよかったの?
Were you interested?
興味あった?
Let's go inside for a moment.
ちょっと 中に出てみよう
It felt so good that I stood up again.
ちょっと気持ちよすぎて、 また立ってきちゃった
Why don't you do it some more?
もうちょっとやらない?
Close your legs,
足閉じて、
I sat down,
ひ じついて、
Something like this happened again.
また こういうの出た
It's true,
ほ んとだ、
amazing.
すごい
What was it like when you took it out inside?
中 でさ、 出した時、どんな感覚だった?
There was.
あったよ
Wait, I put out a lot.
待って、 いっぱい出しちゃったって
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt so good that I let it out twice.
気持ちよすぎてさ、 2回出しちゃった
Then, try one more time on your elbows with your legs spread apart.
じゃあ 足広げたまま、 ひじついてもう一回
Would you like me to do a double piece?
ダブルピースしてもらおうか